NOWFEEL SAFI

Backend Developer

Lille, France - 25 Years Old

PROFILE

During this past 3 years, my purpose was to learn as much as possible about software engineering.

Today and for the rest of my career, my objective is to use the different skills I acquired to contribute to projects that can build and will build a better society.

And Also to keep learning, because I'm convinced that we never stop learning.

CONTACT

- +33658513177
- @ nowfeel.safi@gmail.com
- (in) www.linkedin.com/in/nowfeelsafi-O294531b5
- https://nowfeel-dev.com/

HARD SKILLS

- Golang
- Python
- French Native
- English B2

SOFT SKILLS

- Curiosity
- Dynamism
- Rigor
- Team Work

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Backend Developer - Golang

CDI I Bliink I Oct. 2024 - Present

- Maintain and build gRPC APIs with Protobuf and Golang integration
- Gateway between client/server with graphQL
- Cron Job, Pub/Sub with Google Cloud
- Unit Testing, Functional Testing
- Punctual tasks using React
- Startup Environment

Internship I Bliink I Dec. 2022 - Sep. 2024 Internship I Groupe Cerise I Nov. 2021 - Ap. 2022

- Client Side Javascript
- · Templating using Twig

FORMATION

Openclassrooms Python Backend Developer Graduation (2022-2024)

RNCP Title Level 6

- 11 technical projects with professional simulation
- Scripting, Web, Scrapping
- Autonomous Learning

Web Developer Graduation (2021-2022)

RNCP Title Level 5

- Javascript development
- 6 technical projects with professional simulation